Ear.
Consciousness.
One of the most important things that one needs to understand about a person is that a person is asleep.
He does not wake up even when he thinks that he has woken up.
His awakening is very fragile.
His awakening is so tiny that it should not be taken into account at all.
His wisdom is not only beautiful, but a completely empty name.
You sleep at night.
You sleep during the day.
From birth to death you continue to move from one image from one dream to another.
But you never really wake up.
Don't fool yourself by waking up just by opening your eyes.
Until you open your eyes again.
Until you learn to see.
Do you see who you are?
Don't think that you are growing up.
This is the greatest visibility that a person lives in.
If you assume that you have woken up, it cannot be that you are making an effort to really wake up.
www.mooji.org